leech360.com 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy | Leech360.Com

### Leech360 Privacy Policy

Leech360.com recognizes that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site: Leech360.com.

The purpose of the Leech360 Site is to provide its Users with an infrastructure which enables the Users to download files from the most popular hosting websites by usage of one Leech360 account. Leech360 links its Users with the file-sharing networks. None of the content is controlled by Leech360 administrators or servers. None of the files stored remotely on the file hoster server, are controlled by Leech360 administrators or servers. You willingly provide us certain personal information, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit from the Leech360 service. If you have any hesitation about providing such information to us or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy, you should not become a Leech360 User.

### The Leech360 Site and Third Party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Leech360 Site. The Site may contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by Leech360. Leech360 has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party site. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third party sites you may access through this Site. By using this Site, you release Leech360 from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party site to which this Site may be linked.

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the Service, the Site and the related features, to administer your subscription and to enable Users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. Below are the types and categories of information that we collect.

### Personal Information Collected

We collect your personal information in the following ways:

### Registration

In order to become a User, you must first create an account on our Site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge is personal information allowing others, including Leech360, to identify you: email address and a password. Your password is sent to you via e-mail which you can change any time by logging into your account and editing your ‘My Details’ section.

### Log Data

When you visit the Site or use the Service, just browsing our servers automatically record information about your use of the Service and your visit to the Site (“Log Data”). The Log Data may include information such as your computers Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, what software you were using, pages of our Site that you visited, the time spent on those pages, information you searched for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Sites technical administration, to improve our Sites functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors needs.

### Cookies

Like most sites, Leech360 uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Leech360 to recognize you as a User when you return to the Leech360 site using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to login to your Leech360 Premium Account. Like the information you enter at registration, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on our Site.

One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged into your Leech360 account. The next time you visit the Leech360 site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the service.

### Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Leech360 site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Leech360. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Leech360 Service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

### Leech360 Communications

Leech360 will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the Leech360 Forum Site or through other means available through the service, including text and other forms of messaging.  
You can change your e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into your “Account” and editing your ‘My Details’ section.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

Leech360 takes the privacy of Users very seriously. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information. For instance, we use credit card processing companies to bill Users for account fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and they are bound by confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

### Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Leech360. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

### Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other web sites. If you choose to visit any third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s web site. The fact that we link to a web site is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party web sites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other web sites you visit.

### Accessing and Changing your Account Information

You can review the information you provided us and make any desired changes to them or to the settings for your Leech360 account including your email at any time by logging in to your account on the Leech360 Site. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, Leech360 may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database.

### Deleting your Account

You can also request to delete your Leech360 account easily and at any time. If you request to delete your Leech360 account, we may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. In order to delete your account please send us your request to info@Leech360.com and your account will be deleted the soonest possible.

### Your Obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations imposed by applicable law and regulations:

You must, at all times, respect the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights which may belong to third parties.  
You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic.  
Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account by Leech360, as we take these principles seriously and consider them to be the basis on which our Users adhere to the Leech360 site and the services which it offers.

### Changes to this Policy

Leech360.com may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.

### How to contact us

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our site coordinator at support@leech360.com.
